HUTHMAN KING

SUMMARY

Full-Stack Web Developer with a love for growing and tackling tough tasks. Perserved through many different paths in life, whether excelling in sports, turning life around, or dealing with coding bugs that keep a coder up all night. Excellent communicator with a Business Admin education. Team player, with a "someone's got to do it" mentality. Empathic and understanding of clients needs, providing consistently excellent service to others.

CONTACT

- kinghuthman@gmail.com
- kinghuthman.me
- **6**095562930
- **♀** New Jersey, USA
- **y** kinghuthman
- in huthman-king-8b7376174/
- kinghuthman

EDUCATION

Iona Aug. 2010 to May College 2014 BBA Business Administration 2014

Lambda July 2018 to School Mar. 2019 Web Development 2019

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript(ES6), Python, C, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MERN(MongoDB, Express.js, React/Redux, Node.js, Knowledge of Good Clinical Practice, Knowledge of the Clinical Monitoring process, Knowledge of FDA regulations

PROJECTS

Symposium (Discussion Board) Feb. 2019 to Mar. 2019 Tech Stack: React | Redux | Node.js | Express | PostgreSQL | Stripe | Auth0

- Discussion board that gives users the ability to create categories, discussions, posts and replies, that they can directly follow.
- Completed over the course of 5 weeks, with a team of 4.
- Profile updates and views are available for users by using Node.js to query data from the PostgreSQL database.

EMPLOYMENT

Lambda School

Remote

Teaching Assistant - Labs 11

Mar. 2019 to Apr. 2019

- Lead next phase of Symposium to expand the project I began in my own Labs experience, consisting of two teams for the next five weeks.
- Track progress of a group of 8- 10 students, providing support as they navigate fast paced curriculum and execute a full project cycle.
- Assist students through the debugging process of their code, offering insight into fixes and offering additional support as needed.
- Perform daily stand-ups, code analysis, and a review of pull requests.

Stage Left Steak/Catherine Lombardi's New Brunswick, NJ Server Apr. 2017 to Apr. 2018

- Provided excellent table side service along with captain's, sommeliers, server assistance, and staff.
- Served a high volume of customers and was entrusted with important clients and large groups.

INC Research

Remote/60% Travel Apr. 2015 to May 2016

Clinical Research Associate

- Responsible for the management of designated clinical trials, including site initiation, and routine monitoring and close out visits.

- Participated in global conference calls and meetings to review progress of ongoing clinical trials.
- Analyzed and evaluated clinical data, to ensure investigator and site compliance with the study drug protocol, overall clinical objectives, and ICH Good Clinical Practice (GCP) guidelines.